I can't believe it's the first time I've seen it
Jason Dreams, they never say
You know I don't wanna die
Tears and smiles become my dreams
I want to live here
Time moves by the heart, stay the same
I don't know I don't wanna die
I want voices that come across the world
The world will be cool
Running to the future, crossing every night
Mid-I-E-Hashine
Wishes on stars, connected forever by
Wishing I got you, let's go now
Until the best morning lights are equal
In the light of shine, painting dreams inside
In the light of light
Even most, we never give up
I can't give up
Together we'll find new futures
I can't believe it's the first time I've seen it
We make love, but we move ahead
My aim is to sue you
Fire burns everything in our hearts
Hold on, we're dead
Time moves by the heart, stay the same
I don't know I don't wanna die
I want voices that come across the world
The world will be cool
Running to the future, crossing every night
Mid-I-E-Hashine
Wishes on stars, connected forever by
Wishing I got you, let's go now
Until the best morning lights are equal
In the light of shine, painting dreams inside
In the light of light
Wishing I got you, let's go now
Until the best morning lights are equal
In the light of light
Beyond the sky, a future shining bright
Beyond the sky, our power changes the world tonight
The world will be cool
Even its warmth talks like remains
Keep on all heat, guide, spread your wings
And fly through the games
The heart will be cool
Running to the future, crossing every night
Mid-I-E-Hashine
Wishes on stars, connected forever by
Wishing I got you, let's go now
Until the best morning lights are equal
In the light of light
Wishing I got you, let's go now
Until the best morning lights are equal
In the light of light
Wishing I got you, let's go now